[Music]
Cult of personality tyrants with
platforms built on defiance. One tweets
wild democracy dice the others use
nationalist lies. Media moles and tech
kings manipulating the puppet strings.
wealth as their measure of worth as they
wonder what's left of the earth.
Unchecked power, dangerous game. Free
speech twisted, never the same. The
public discourse in flames while they
absolve themselves of blame. All the
guards in power suits feeding lies to
their recruits. Democracy hangs by a
threat while propaganda fills your head.
Truth decays.
[Music]
Silicon Valley billionaires
manipulate the truth. No one cares.
Media empires bought and sold. Attention
spans controlled and trolls. Corporate
pings with golden thrones punching tight
to their smartphones. The people's voice
grows ever weak. Best platform sensor
who can speak.
The constitution gathering dust while
it's all due to fear and trust.
Algorithm shape narrative flow. Tell me
how low we go. All our guards in power
suits being lies to their recruits.
Democracy hangs violent while propaganda
fills your head.
Truth be
truth.
[Music]
[Applause]